Charles N Watson

612 South College Avenue (Apartment B), Oxford, OH 45056 (208) 921-0464 | nchlswtsn@gmail.com

Recent graduate with a BA in international studies focused in international economics and Russian language. A hardworking and focused individual, hoping to join a team of dedicated professionals working collaboratively toward achieving company goals. Extremely reliable with a passion for research, constant learning, and exploring new ideas.

Education

Miami University - Oxford, Ohio August 2013 - May 2015

BA in international studies

Regional Focus: Russia and Central Eurasia Minors: Economics and Russian Language

Thinkful Academy – Web School January 2015 - May 2015

Skills: Python, HTML, CSS, SQL, continuous integration, Flask/Django Frameworks

Themes: Web scraping, web design, APIs, user experience, user interface,

Personal Projects: elitecatch.com, Tesla Motors data spiders, SpaceX data spiders, Hackernews data spiders, Stock Investment tools

Daugavpils University - Daugavpils, Latvia June 2014 - August 2014

Courses: Russian syntax, morphology, international business

Wittenberg University - Springfield, Ohio August 2011 - May 2013

International Student Committee member
Professor Effectiveness Committee member
Student Athletic Advisory Committee member
Varsity Men's Track and Field team captain
Recognized on the Dean's List
Recognized as a Provost Scholar
Recognized as a "Tiger Top 25" (University's 25 highest athlete GPAs)

Recognized as Most Inspirational Player - Men's Track Team

Work Experience

Miami University IT Department August 2014 - May 2015 Oxford, Ohio

Skills Developed: Management systems, cross departmental collaboration, time management

Miami University Apple Store October 2013 - May 2015 Oxford, Ohio

Skills Developed: Customer service, sales, marketing, collaboration

Daugavpils University June 2014 - August 2014 Daugavpils, Latvia

Skills Developed: Patience, strong communication, planning, organization, Russian language

Wittenberg University Admission Office September 2012 - June 2013 Springfield, Ohio

Skills Developed: Recruiting tactics, Microsoft Office Suite, punctuality, verbal and written communication

Referrals available upon request